<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Container version="2">
  <Name>orb-sensor</Name>
  <Repository>orbforge/orb:latest</Repository>
  <Registry>https://hub.docker.com/r/orbforge/orb</Registry>
  <Network>host</Network>
  <MyIP/>
  <Shell>sh</Shell>
  <Privileged>false</Privileged>
  <Support>https://github.com/orbforge/orb-issues</Support>
  <Project>https://orb.net/</Project>
  <Overview>Orb is an intelligent app &amp;amp; platform designed to help you understand and improve your internet connectivity&#xD;
&#xD;
Real-time Monitoring: Orb continuously monitors your network connection to provide up-to-date insights.&#xD;
Comprehensive Metrics: Track the responsiveness, reliability, and speed of your internet connection.&#xD;
Multi-platform Support: Available on iOS, Android, macOS, and Windows.&#xD;
Multiple Sensor Options: Monitor from your personal devices or set up dedicated Orb Sensors for 24/7 monitoring.&#xD;
Historical Data: View trends and patterns in your network performance over time.&#xD;
Actionable Insights: Receive suggestions to improve your connectivity based on detected issues.&#xD;
&#xD;
Further details available here: https://orb.net/docs/getting-started/what-is-orb</Overview>
  <Category>Tools: Network:Management</Category>
  <WebUI/>
  <TemplateURL/>
  <Icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/TheMapledCog/unraid-templates/refs/heads/main/orb-sensor/favicon.png</Icon>
  <ExtraParams>--memory="512m"</ExtraParams>
  <PostArgs/>
  <CPUset/>
  <DateInstalled>1746275012</DateInstalled>
  <DonateText/>
  <DonateLink/>
  <Requires>network_mode: host: This is crucial for Orb to monitor network traffic directly from the host's network interfaces.&#xD;
Port: 7443 and 8081 to be available on your Unraid host&#xD;
Note: There is a memory limit set of 512m by default&#xD;
&#xD;
Once the Orb container is running, Open the Orb app on your phone or computer (which must be on the same network).&#xD;
Your new Docker-based Orb sensor should be automatically detected and appear in the app, ready to be linked to your account. Follow the prompts in the app to link it.</Requires>
  <Config Name="orb-data" Target="/root/.config/orb" Default="" Mode="rw" Description="Persists Orb configuration" Type="Path" Display="always" Required="true" Mask="false"/>
</Container>